question_data =  [
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia is the irrational fear of long words.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "The M41 Walker Bulldog remains in service in some countries to this day.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Shrimp can swim backwards.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The longest place named in the United States is Lake Chargoggagoggmanchauggagoggchaubunagungamaugg, located near Webster, MA.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The bikini is named after the &quot;Bikini Atoll&quot;, an island where the United States conducted tests on atomic bombs.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Cucumbers are usually more than 90% water.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "The Xenomorph from the science fiction film &quot;Alien&quot; has acidic blood.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Scientists accidentally killed the once known world&#039;s oldest living creature, a mollusc, known to be aged as 507 years old.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "There exists an island named &quot;Java&quot;.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Vehicles", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "When BMW was established in 1916, it was producing automobiles.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The capital of the US State Ohio is the city of Chillicothe.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "In the periodic table, Potassium&#039;s symbol is the letter K.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In Riot Games &quot;League of Legends&quot; the name of Halloween event is called &quot;The Reckoning&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "A &#039;Millinillion&#039; is a real number.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Klingons respect their disabled comrades, and those who are old, injuried, and helpless.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;League of Legends&quot;, there exists four different types of Dragon.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In the Season One Championship of &quot;League of Legends&quot;, the highest achievable rank was Diamond.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Vehicles", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The majority of Subaru vehicles are made in China.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In career mode of &quot;Need for Speed: Underground 2&quot;, the first car the player can drive is the BMW M3 GTR.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Sir Issac Newton served as a Member of Parliament, but the only recorded time he spoke was to complain about a draft in the chambers.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Popcorn was invented in 1871 by Frederick W. Rueckheim in the USA where he sold the snack on the streets of Chicago.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Jeb Bush was elected as Governor of Florida in 2002, starting his political career.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Franz Joseph I was the last emperor of Austria.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The game Garry&#039;s Mod originally took assets and codes from the popular Half Life 2 mod JBmod.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The original ending of &quot;Little Shop Of Horrors&quot; has the plants taking over the world.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]